<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.uog.edu/rss-feed" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/rss-feed</link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en</language>
          <item>
    <title>UOG Women&amp;#039;s Soccer Is Defeated 4-1 By FC Familia</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/news-announcements/uog-womens-soccer-is-defeated-4-1-by-fc-familia</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; height=&quot;956&quot; width=&quot;1500&quot; class=&quot;media-element file-default&quot; typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_03.26-vs-fc-familia_1500.jpg&quot; /&gt;The University of Guam Women&#039;s Soccer Team was defeated on Sunday 4-1 by FC Familia in a Guam Football Association Women&#039;s Division II 9-on-9 Match at the GFA National Training Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The UOG Squad played with the minimum 9 players on Sunday and was forced to play goal keepers out of position due to the lack of players. The high scoring FC Famila team started out well in the first 10 minutes of the match, having several chances at a goal. Tey were stopped by the UOG goalkeeper and defense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The match settled down for the next 15-20 minutes, and UOG was able to keep Famila out of their goal box area. But the Tritons also struggled with goal chances as well. Having one set shot from about 20 yards out hit the top of goal was as close as they would come to score in the middle of the first half.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But both teams broke through in the final 10 minutes of the half, with FC Familia scoring first. UOG came right back to score as well and go into half-time tied 1-1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2nd half was all FC Familia, as UOG started to suffer muscle cramps and fatigue. The Familia with its deeper bench was able to score three times. UOG was forced to play with 8 players at times due to muscle cramps and no one on the bench to replace them. UOG was unable to put together any offensive runs at goal as the team wore down in the final 40 minutes of the match.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Tritons are now 1-2-0 in the league and return to action next &lt;strong&gt;Sunday, April 9, at 6:30 p.m. against Team Mosa’s&lt;/strong&gt; at the GFA National Training Center. This is UOG&#039;s final regular season game in the league, GFA Playoffs start on April 23.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Mon, 2017-03-27 09:17</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Mon, 2017-03-27 09:17</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17402</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The UOG Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team Wins Federation Match 2-1</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/news-announcements/the-uog-womens-volleyball-team-wins-federation-match-2-1</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; height=&quot;497&quot; width=&quot;321&quot; style=&quot;float: right; margin: 15px;&quot; class=&quot;media-element file-default&quot; typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_volleyball-vs-pokai-jr_1500_0.jpg&quot; /&gt;The University of Guam Women&#039;s Volleyball Team defeated Pokai Jr.’s 2-1 in the Guam Volleyball Federation League on Friday night at the &quot;Jungle&quot; on the Father Duenas Memorial School campus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lady Tritons played in a dominating style in the first set, not letting Pokai Jr.’s develop any offense as UOG won the game 25-8 to go up 1-0.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2nd set was much different. UOG was behind the whole start of the match. The Lady Tritons inally caught up at 10-10 but could never move ahead or gain real momentum. In the closing points of the match, UOG hurt itself with multiple service errors, which included the final point at 26-26. UOG served the ball into the net, and Pokai Jr.&#039;s had the set 27-26 per the &quot;Sudden Death&quot; rule (sets to 25 end when the first team scores 27 points regardless of a 2 point lead or not.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 3rd set to 15 points, UOG took an early lead 6-4, but Pokai Jr&#039;s went on a 6-point run to lead 10-6. UOG battled back and caught up at 11-11. But Pokai Jr.&#039;s again made a run, and UOG found itself down to a match point for Pokai Jr.&#039;s 14-12. The Tritons ran off 4 straight points to win 16-14.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UOG is now 3-2 in the Federation League and plays again on &lt;strong&gt;Thursday, March 30 at 7:00 p.m. against Au Mana&lt;/strong&gt; back in the Jungle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/142714024@N03/albums/72157678471188494&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;SEE PHOTOS&amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Mon, 2017-03-27 09:03</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Mon, 2017-03-27 09:03</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17401</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Triton Farm Selling Fresh Eggs</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/news-announcements/triton-farm-selling-fresh-eggs</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#212121&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 12pt;&quot;&gt;Triton Farm is selling eggs for $5 per dozen. The eggs are from free-range Long Island breed chickens. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#212121&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 12pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; height=&quot;204&quot; width=&quot;204&quot; style=&quot;float: right; margin: 15px 20px;&quot; class=&quot;media-element file-default&quot; typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_eggs_400.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#212121&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 12pt;&quot;&gt;For more information, contact Jason at 787-2144. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Fri, 2017-03-24 13:50</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Fri, 2017-03-24 13:50</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17400</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>TracDat V End User Training</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/tracdat-v-end-user-training</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; height=&quot;2200&quot; width=&quot;1700&quot; style=&quot;width: 427px; height: 532px;&quot; class=&quot;media-element file-wysiwyg&quot; typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/tracdat_end_user_training2-1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-23 11:27</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-23 11:27</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17398</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Pacific Asia Inquiry Calls for Submissions</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/news-announcements/pacific-asia-inquiry-calls-for-submissions</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The editorial board of the Pacific Asia Inquiry invites submissions of linguistics-focused articles, critical essays, and case studies (both applied and theoretical) specific to the Pacific Islands and Asia regions for possible publication in Volume 8. Submissions from across the liberal arts and social sciences are also welcome. The Pacific Asia Inquiry is a peer-reviewed, multidisciplinary journal published online by the University of Guam College of Liberal Arts and Social Sciences. It features in-depth studies on the Pacific and adjacent Asia, particularly including the Mariana Islands and greater Micronesia. Contributors are invited not only to share their innovative research but also to challenge extant positions and perspectives. Any theoretical or methodological approach may be employed so long as it is documented in a readable style of writing that is accessible to specialists and non-specialists alike. &lt;strong&gt;The deadline for submissions is July 15, 2017.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; height=&quot;388&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; style=&quot;float: right; margin: 15px 20px;&quot; class=&quot;media-element file-default&quot; typeof=&quot;foaf:Image&quot; src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/PAI-Cover_0.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUBMISSION PROCEDURES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;Include the following as three separate files:&lt;br&gt;1) a cover page, which includes authors’ names, titles, affiliations, and addresses, including street and e-mail addresses;&lt;br&gt;2) a title page, which includes the title of the article and an abstract of the paper (the abstract should be no more than 150 words); and&lt;br&gt;3) the main text, including photos, tables, figures, media, and references.&lt;br&gt;Our blind peer-review process requires that authors’ names and addresses appear only on the cover page. No identifying information may appear in the abstract or text itself. Relevant publications, including those written by the authors, may appear in the reference section as long as nothing is said to connect the reference with the authors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL SUBMISSION GUIDELINES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;br&gt;Submissions should not exceed 10,000 words, including tables and references. Please follow the conventions of the Publication Manual of the American Psychological Association (6th ed., 2009), or the MLA Style Manual and Guide to Scholarly Publishing (7th ed., 2009). Indent the first word of a paragraph by half an inch or five spaces (one “tab”), and number all pages consecutively, putting numbers in the lower right-hand corner. Figures, tables, and photos should be inserted into manuscript at the time of initial submittal, and they need to be appropriately titled, sourced, and numbered consecutively. Endnotes should be used and references should appear at the end of the paper. Do not insert automatic formatting anywhere in the manuscript. Additional guidelines apply. Please visit http://www.uog.edu/schools-and-colleges/college-of-liberal- arts-and-social-sciences/publications/pacific-asia-inquiry-4 for full guidelines and for access to previous volumes of Pacific Asia Inquiry, which may be used as a general reference. Please be advised that this is a venue for scholarly essays. Fiction and poetry submissions will not be entertained.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forward inquiries and submissions electronically to:&lt;br&gt;Dr. Avizia Long, Co-Editor&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:longa@triton.uog.edu&quot;&gt;longa@triton.uog.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Tue, 2017-03-21 13:44</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Tue, 2017-03-21 13:44</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17397</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Students Receive Travel Awards</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/news-announcements/uog-students-receive-travel-awards</link>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The following six University of Guam students received travel awards from the Research Corporation of the University of Guam (RCUOG) and will spend a part of the spring or summer immersed in interests related to their degree program. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were able to offer travel awards to assist students in getting to their destinations using mileage accrued from purchases made with the RCUOG official credit card in accordance with Public Law 32-019,”said Cathleen Moore-Linn, interim executive director of RCUOG. “RCUOG continues to unlock opportunities for UOG students and researchers, supporting them in their endeavors, which results in positive outcomes for Guam and the region,” she added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Student Awardees&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_ida-shalilian-_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;Ida Shalilian&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin: 10px 15px;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9588&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ida Shalilian&lt;/strong&gt; successfully defended her thesis in Environmental Science in January and will return to Guam from her hometown of Houston to continue her research on her thesis topic, which, according to her advisor Dr. John Jenson, focused on “innovative field measurement and discovery of an extraordinary volume of freshwater discharge estimated to be 5.3 million gallons of per day, flowing from a cave on Guam.” She will validate her initial work with additional high tech measurements. She is expected to finalize her technical report and prepare her manuscript for journal publication as well as present her thesis to the Guam Waterworks Authority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_katlyn-sutherland_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;Katlyn Sutherland&quot; style=&quot;margin: 10px 15px; float: right;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9590&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_-joleen-una_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;Joleen Unas&quot; style=&quot;margin: 10px 15px; float: left;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9589&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joleen Unas&lt;/strong&gt;, Fine Arts and Computer Science major, and &lt;strong&gt;Katlyn Sutherland&lt;/strong&gt;, Fine Arts major, were both selected to represent UOG at the Zureta- the Misprint Exhibition held at the Chinretsukan Art Gallery at Tokyo University of the Arts in May. This printmaking show receives submissions from twenty universities from around the world. Throughout the year the show will travel to other countries. Unas and Sutherland will also participate in the International Printmaking Symposium, which is being held in conjunction with the exhibit. “Attending and participating in international events like this is a great opportunity for students to meet with other artists who share the same passion,” said Sutherland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_james-fifer_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;James Fifer&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin: 10px 15px;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9591&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;James Fifer&lt;/strong&gt;, graduate student in Marine Biology, will travel to England to continue research on an emerging coral disease discovered by UOG Marine Lab’s Dr. Laurie Raymundo. He will participate in the analysis and sampling of DNA, RNA and protein cells, which are essential steps in the study of a new coral disease. James will work in Dr. Mike Sweet’s laboratory at the University of Derby in England. Dr. Sweet and Dr. Raymundo are partners in this research project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_cassandra-jay-flores-hughes_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;Cassandra-Jay Flores-Hughes&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin: 10px 15px;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9592&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cassandra-Jay Flores-Hughes&lt;/strong&gt;, Education major, has a strong interest in developing a set of courses centered on climate change that is culturally relevant to the region. The RCUOG travel award will allow her to participate in the Pacific Education Conference in Palau this July, where she will learn more about developing climate science curriculum and lesson plans to use at the high school level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.uog.edu/sites/default/files/2017_cameron-dudkiewicz_205x270.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University of Guam&quot; title=&quot;Cameron Dudkiewicz&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin: 10px 15px;&quot; class=&quot;caption&quot; fid=&quot;9593&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cameron Dudkiewicz&lt;/strong&gt;, majoring in Business Administration with a concentration in Human Resources, will attend the Society for Human Resources Management national conference in New Orleans this June. He will have the opportunity to network with HR professionals from around the world and across the USA. Upon his return, Cameron will give a presentation to other business students at UOG about his experience at the largest Human Resources Management conference in the world&lt;/p&gt;</description>
     <pubDate>Tue, 2017-03-21 13:18</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Tue, 2017-03-21 13:18</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17396</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Au Mana </title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-au-mana-0</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Mon, 2017-03-20 08:27</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Mon, 2017-03-20 08:27</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17394</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Nex Gen</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-nex-gen</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 15:02</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 15:02</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17391</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Haggan Neni&amp;#039;s</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-haggan-nenis</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 15:01</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 15:01</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17390</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Getpan</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-getpan</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:59</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:59</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17389</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Au Mana</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-au-mana</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:57</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:57</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17388</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Pokai Jr.&amp;#039;s</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-pokai-jrs-0</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:56</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:56</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17387</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs La Femme</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-la-femme</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:55</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:55</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17386</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Haggen</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-haggen</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:53</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:53</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17385</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Metgot</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-metgot</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:51</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:51</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17384</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Volleyball Team vs Pokai Jr.&amp;#039;s</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-volleyball-team-vs-pokai-jrs</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:49</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:49</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17383</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Women&amp;#039;s Soccer Team Championship / 3rd Place</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/womens-soccer-team-championship-3rd-place</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:46</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:46</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17382</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Women&amp;#039;s Soccer Team Round 1 Playoffs</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/womens-soccer-team-round-1-playoffs</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:44</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:44</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17381</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Soccer Team vs Team Mosa&amp;#039;s</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-soccer-team-vs-team-mosas</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:42</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:42</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17380</guid>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>UOG Tritons Women&amp;#039;s Soccer Team vs FC Familia</title>
    <link>http://www.uog.edu/events/uog-tritons-womens-soccer-team-vs-fc-familia</link>
    <description></description>
     <pubDate>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:40</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>Thu, 2017-03-16 14:40</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">17379</guid>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>